{
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "What is Sora's last name?",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "1": "Amatsume",
            "2": "Shiba",
            "3": "Kasugano",
            "4": "It is not stated",
            "answer": "Kasugano"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is Motoka last name?",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "1": "Kasugano",
            "2": "Yorihime",
            "3": "Nogisaka",
            "4": "Migiwa",
            "answer": "Nogisaka"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is Akira's last name?",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "1": "Kasugano",
            "2": "Amatsume",
            "3": "She doesn't have one",
            "4": "Yorihime",
            "answer": "Amatsume"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is Yahiro's last name?",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "1": "Yorihime ",
            "2": "Ifukube",
            "3": "Migiwa",
            "4": "Kasugano",
            "answer" :"Ifukube"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is Nao's last name?",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "1": "Amatsume",
            "2": "Yorihime",
            "3": "Nogisaka",
            "4": "It is never stated",
            "answer": "Yorihime"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is Kazuha's last name?",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "1": "Migiwa",
            "2": "Tatsuya",
            "3": "Nogisaka",
            "4": "Dola",
            "answer": "Migiwa"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is Class Rep's real name?",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "1": "Kazuha",
            "2": "Kozue",
            "3": "Shiba",
            "4": "It is not stated.",
            "answer": "Kozue"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is Class Rep's last name?",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "1": "It is not stated",
            "2": "Migiwa",
            "3": "Ifukube",
            "4": "Kuranaga",
            "answer": "Kuranaga"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is Ryouhei's last name?",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "1": "Nakazato",
            "2": "It is never stated",
            "3": "Chikara",
            "4": "Ifukube",
            "answer": "Nakazato"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is Haru's last name?",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "1": "Kuranaga",
            "2": "Nakazato",
            "3": "Kasugano",
            "4": "Migiwa",
            "answer": "Kasugano"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who gave Sora her stuffed bunny in the anime?",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "1": "She bought it herself",
            "2": "Haru",
            "3": "Her father",
            "4": "Her mother",
            "answer": "her mother"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who gave Sora her stuffed bunny in the manga?",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "1": "Her Mother",
            "2": "Haru",
            "3": "It is not stated",
            "4": "Ryouhei",
            "answer": "Haru"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the relationship between Kazuha and Akira?",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "1": "Sisters",
            "2": "Possible lovers",
            "3": "classmates",
            "4": "All of the above",
            "answer": "All of the above"
        },
        {
            "question": "Why did Haru and Sora move back to the countryside?",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "1": "To get away from the city",
            "2": "Their parents died",
            "3": "Summer break",
            "4": "They always lived there",
            "answer": "Their parents died"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which girl is the shortest?",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "1": "Akira",
            "2": "Sora",
            "3": "Class Rep",
            "4": "Nao",
            "answer": "Sora"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which girl is the tallest?",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "1": "Nao",
            "2": "Yahiro",
            "3": "Kazuha",
            "4": "Motoka",
            "answer": "Yahiro"
        },
        {
            "question": "T/F the locations presented in YnS are based on real life locations?",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "1": "True",
            "2": "False",
            "answer": "True"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which girl is only an unlockable route in the VN?",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "1": "Akira",        
            "2": "Class Rep",
            "3": "Sora",
            "4": "They are all available by default",
            "answer": "Sora"
        },
        {
            "question": "How old is Sora implied to be?",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "1": "16",
            "2": "17",
            "3": "18",
            "4": "12",
            "answer": "16"
        },
        {
            "question": "How old is Akira implied to be?",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "1": "14",
            "2": "16",
            "3": "17",
            "4": "18",
            "answer": "16"
        },
        {
            "question": "How old is Nao implied to be?",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "1": "16",
            "2": "17",
            "3": "18",
            "4": "19",
            "answer": "17"
        },
        {
            "question": "How old is Ryouhei implied to be?",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "1": "17",
            "2": "18",
            "3": "19",
            "4": "30",
            "answer": "17"
        },
        {
            "question": "How old is Kazuha implIed to be?",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "1": "16",
            "2": "17",
            "3": "18",
            "4": "19",
            "answer": "16"
        },
        {
            "question": "How old is Class rep implied to be?",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "1": "16",
            "2": "17",
            "3": "18",
            "4": "30",
            "answer": "16"
        },
        {
            "question": "How old is Yahiro implied to be?",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "1": "16",
            "2": "17",
            "3": "18",
            "4": "28",
            "answer": "28"
        },
        {
            "question": "How old is Motoka implied to be?",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "1": "16",
            "2": "18",
            "3": "20",
            "4": "26",
            "answer": "26"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which Scandanavian country did Sora and Haru move to after the events of Yosuga no Sora?",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "1": "Estonia",
            "2": "Finland",
            "3": "Sweden",
            "4": "The exact country is not stated.",
            "answer": "The exact country is not stated"
        },
        {
            "question": "What year was the Yosuga no Sora VN released?",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "1": "2007",
            "2": "2008",
            "3": "2009",
            "4": "2010",
            "answer": "2008"
        },
        {
            "question": "What year was the anime released?",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "1": "2008",
            "2": "2009",
            "3": "2010",
            "4": "2011",
            "answer": "2010"
        },
        {
            "question": "When is Sora's birthday?",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "1": "Febuary 5th",
            "2": "May 9th",
            "3": "December 23rd",
            "4": "September 1st",
            "answer": "February 5th"
        },
        {
            "question": "When is Akira's birthday? Hint. Akira and Kazuha have the same birthday.",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "1": "August 8th",
            "2": "September 25th",
            "3": "November 1st",
            "4": "August 3rd",
            "answer": "August 3rd"
        },
        {
            "question": "When is Nao's birthday? Hint. Nao and Ryouhei have the same birthday",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "1": "Febuary 5th",
            "2": "March 15th",
            "3": "June 11th",
            "4": "October 7th",
            "answer": "October 7th"
        },
        {
            "question": "When is Ryouhei's birthday? Hint. Nao and Ryouhei have the exact same birthday.",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "1": "Febuary 5th",
            "2": "July 4th",
            "3": "October 7th",
            "4": "December 1st",
            "answer": "October 7th"
        },
        {
            "question": "When is Haru's birthday?",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "1": "Febuary 1st",
            "2": "April 1st",
            "3": "Febuary 5th",
            "4": "January 11th",
            "answer": "Febuary 5th"
        },
        {
            "question": "When is Kazuha's birthday? Hint. Akira and Kazuha have the same birthday.",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "1": "August 3rd",
            "2": "January 1st",
            "3": "November 1st",
            "4": "Febuary 29th",
            "answer": "August 3rd"
        },
        {
            "question": "When is Class Rep's birthday?",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "1": "It is not stated",
            "2": "June 1",
            "3": "June 14th",
            "4": "April 11th",
            "answer": "June 1"
        },
        {
            "question": "When is Yahiro's birthday?",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "1": "January 9th",
            "2": "April 25th",
            "3": "Setember 11th",
            "4": "January 10th",
            "answer": "January 10th"
        },
        {
            "question": "How long has the English translation project for the VN gone on?",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "1": "1 year",
            "2": "5 years",
            "3": "Over a decade",
            "4": "8 years",
            "answer": "Over a decade"
        },
        {
            "question": "What was the company that made the Yosuga no Sora VN?",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "1": "Sphere",
            "2": "Madbox",
            "3": "Eight Bit",
            "4": "Nintendo",
            "answer": "Sphere"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the name of the orange cat that often appears in the series?",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "1": "Master",
            "2": "Mr. whiskers",
            "3": "Shishou",
            "4": "A name is never given",
            "answer": "shishou"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the name of the lake that Sora almost drowns in?",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "1": "Lake Hakone",
            "2": "Lake Yokohama",
            "3": "Lake of the goddess",
            "4": "None of the above",
            "answer": "Lake Hakone "
        },
        {
            "question": "Who raped Haru?",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "1": "Sora",
            "2": "Nao",
            "3": "Ryouhei",
            "4": "Motoka",
            "answer": "Nao"
        },
        {
            "question": "Why did Sora and Haru's parents die?",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "1": "Drug overdose",
            "2": "Mysteriously disapeared",
            "3": "Car accident",
            "4": "Drowning",
            "answer": "car accident"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of these girls has black hair?",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "1": "Nao",
            "2": "Akira",
            "3": "Motoka",
            "4": "Yahiro",
            "answer": "Nao"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of these girls has red hair?",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "1": "Akira",
            "2": "Motoka",
            "3": "Kazuha",
            "4": "All of the above",
            "answer": "Motoka"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of these girls has brown hair?",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "1": "Motoka",
            "2": "Nao",
            "3": "Sora",
            "4": "Akira",
            "answer": "Akira"
        },
        {
            "question": "Where does Yosuga no Sora take place?",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "1": "Tokyo",
            "2": "Rural Japan",
            "3": "Finland",
            "4": "Another planet",
            "answer": "Rural Japan"
        },
        {
            "question": "What instrument does Kazuha play?",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "1": "Violin",
            "2": "Viola",
            "3": "Piano",
            "4": "She doesn't play an instrument",
            "answer": "Viola"
        },
        {
            "question": "What does Sora always carry with her?",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "1": "A necklace to remind her of her mother",
            "2": "A purse",
            "3": "A stuffed bunny",
            "4": "A chess piece",
            "answer": "A stuffed bunny"
        },
        {
            "question": "How many volumes does the YnS manga have?",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "1": "One",
            "2": "Two",
            "3": "Three",
            "4": "Four",
            "answer": "Two"
        },
        {
            "question": "How many chapters does the YnS manga have?",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "1": "5",
            "2": "10",
            "3": "14",
            "4": "20",
            "answer": "14"
        },
        {
            "question": "What occupation does Motoka hold?",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "1": "Nurse",
            "2": "Teacher",
            "3": "Prostitute",
            "4": "Maid",
            "answer": "Maid"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who catches Sora and Haru having sex?",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "1": "Kazuha and Akira",
            "2": "Ryouhei",
            "3": "Their parents",
            "4": "Kozue and Nao",
            "answer": "Kozue and Nao"
        },
        {
            "question": "What are the 2 new routes in Haruka na Sora?",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "1": "Sora and Kozue",
            "2": "Sora and Yahiro",
            "3": "Yahiro and Kozue",
            "4": "Ryouhei and Haru",
            "answer": "Yahiro and Kozue"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who helped Haru look for Sora when she went missing in the anime?",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "1": "Nao",
            "2": "All of the main cast",
            "3": "Akira",
            "4": "He was on his own",
            "answer": "Nao"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who helped Haru look for Sora when she was missing in the manga?",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "1": "Nao",
            "2": "All of the main cast",
            "3": "Akira",
            "4": "Ryouhei",
            "answer": "All of the main cast"
        },
        {
            "question": "How large is the Yosuga no Sora chinese community?",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "1": "100 members",
            "2": "100k members",
            "3": "400k members",
            "4": "1 million members",
            "answer": "400k members"
        },
        {
            "question": "How did Sora and Haru survive drowning?",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "1": "Haru saved them",
            "2": "Akira saved them",
            "3": "Nao saved them",
            "4": "Sora saved them",
            "answer": "Sora saved them"
        },
        {
            "question": "Where did Sora try to run away to with Haru in the manga?",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "1": "Tokoyo",
            "2": "Norway",
            "3": "Hazumi-Hazumi",
            "4": "No where in particular",
            "answer": "Hazumi-Hazumi"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who did Haru end up with in the manga?",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "1": "No one",
            "2": "Sora",
            "3": "There are several different endings",
            "4": "Akira",
            "answer": "Sora"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which girl has the smallest boobs?",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "1": "Akira",
            "2": "Nao",
            "3": "Kazuha",
            "4": "Sora",
            "answer": "Sora"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which girl wears glasses?",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "1": "Kazuha",
            "2": "Class rep",
            "3": "Nao",
            "4": "Sora",
            "answer": "Nao"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which girl is the shortest?",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "1": "Sora",
            "2": "Akira",
            "3": "Class rep",
            "4": "Yahiro",
            "answer": "Sora"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which girl is the tallest?",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "1": "Motoka",
            "2": "Sora",
            "3": "Kazuha",
            "4": "Yahiro",
            "answer": "Yahiro"
        },
        {
            "question": "Why can't Haru swim?",
            "difficulty": "m",
            "1": "He just never learned",
            "2": "He is traumatised by nearly drowning when he was younger",
            "3": "Nao sabotaged his lessons",
            "4": "He can swim",
            "answer": "He is traumatised by nearly drowning when he was younger"
        },
        {
            "question": "When did Kozue fall in love with Haru?",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "1": "When they were kids",
            "2": "First sight when Haru returned",
            "3": "During his time at school",
            "4": "After seeing him and Sora having sex",
            "answer": "First sight when Haru returned"
        },
        {
            "question": "How did Kozue react to catching Haru and Sora in the manga?",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "1": "Horrified",
            "2": "Turned on",
            "3": "Jealous",
            "4": "Uncomfortable but accepting",
            "answer": "Uncomfortable but accepting"
        },
        {
            "question": "What role does Motoka play in the manga?",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "1": "Main character",
            "2": "Side character",
            "3": "Cameo",
            "4": "She isn't in the manga",
            "answer": "She isn't in the manga"
        },
        {
            "question": "Why did Haru slap Sora in the anime?",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "1": "There was a misquito on her face",
            "2": "She suggested an abortion",
            "3": "She insulted him",
            "4": "She cheated on him",
            "answer": "She suggested an abortion"
        },
        {
            "question": "Why did Sora slap Haru in the anime?",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "1": "There was a a misquito on his face",
            "2": "He cheated on her",
            "3": "He was being an idiot",
            "4": "She never slapped him",
            "answer": "There was a misquito on his face"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is Sora's favourite meal?",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "1": "Ice cream",
            "2": "Shushi",
            "3": "Ramen",
            "4": "Curry",
            "answer": "Curry"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which character did Haru marry at the end of the anime?",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "1": "Motoka",
            "2": "Nao",
            "3": "Sora",
            "4": "No one",
            "answer": "Motoka"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the runtime of Yosuga no Sora?",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "1": "103 minutes",
            "2": "212 minutes",
            "3": "909 minutes",
            "4": "300 minutes",
            "answer": "300 minutes"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which episodes comprise Sora's route?",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "1": "One, two, three, four",
            "2": "One, seven, ten, eleven, twelve",
            "3": "Ten, eleven, twelve",
            "4": "All of season 2",
            "answer": "One, seven, ten, eleven, twelve"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which episodes comprise Nao's route?",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "1": "One, two, three, four",
            "2": "One, four, five",
            "3": "One, seven, eight, nine",
            "4": "One, seven, ten, eleven, twelve",
            "answer": "One, seven, eight, nine"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which episodes Kazuha's route?",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "1": "One, two, three, four",
            "2": "Two, five, six",
            "3": "Nine, ten, eleven, twelve",
            "4": "One, seven, ten, eleven, twelve",
            "answer": "One, two, three, four"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which episode's comprise Akira's route?",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "1": "One, two, five, six",
            "2": "One, two, three, four",
            "3": "Seven, eight, nine",
            "4": "Three, Four",
            "answer": "One, two, five, six"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which episodes Comprise Motoka's route?",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "1": "She doesn't appear in the anime",
            "2": "All of them but only in the ending omakes",
            "3": "13, 14, 15, 16",
            "4": "7, 8, 9",
            "answer": "All of them, but only in the ending omakes"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of these is used as a nickname for Akira?",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "1": "Aki",
            "2": "Amatsume",
            "3": "Nyoume",
            "4": "She is only ever referred to as Akira",
            "answer": "Nyome"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who does the cat belong to?",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "1": "Sora",
            "2": "Akira",
            "3": "Nao",
            "4": "Kazuha",
            "answer": "Akira"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who shows Haru the way to school in the VN?",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "1": "Nao",
            "2": "Akira",
            "3": "Kazuha",
            "4": "He has to figure it out himself",
            "answer": "Nao"
        },
        {
            "question": "Why did Nao rape Haru?",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "1": "Pure lust",
            "2": "Stress due to her parents fighting",
            "3": "To assert dominance",
            "4": "To upset Sora",
            "answer": "Stress due to her parents fighting"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who told Sora the legendary story about the lake that inspired Sora to commit Suicide?",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "1": "Nao",
            "2": "Akira",
            "3": "Kazuha",
            "4": "Class rep",
            "answer": "Akira"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the name of the goddess of lake behind Akira's shrine?",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "1": "Sayorihime-sama",
            "2": "Kasugano",
            "3": "Tet",
            "4": "Aqua",
            "answer": "Sayorihime-sama"
        },
        {
            "question": "What does Yosuga no Sora mean?",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "1": "Incest is wincest",
            "2": "Sky of connections",
            "3": "Under the endless sky",
            "4": "The story of a girl named Sora",
            "answer": "Sky of connections"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who else plays Viola besides Kazuha?",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "1": "Akira",
            "2": "Nao",
            "3": "Kazuha's Father",
            "4": "Kazuha's Mother",
            "answer": "Kazuha's Mother"
        },
        {
            "question": "What position was Nao in when she raped Haru?",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "1": "Missionary",
            "2": "cowgirl",
            "3": "Reverse cowgirl",
            "4": "T-POSE",
            "answer": "Cowgirl"
        },
        {
            "question": "The director of the Yosuga no Sora anime also directed:",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "1": "School days",
            "2": "Aki Sora",
            "3": "No Game No Life",
            "4": "Mahouka",
            "answer": "Aki Sora"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who is The Catcher-Killer?",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "1": "Akira",
            "2": "Ryouhei",
            "3": "Kazuha",
            "4": "Kozue",
            "answer": "Akira"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is Akira favorite type of bread?",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "1": "Pumpkin",
            "2": "Rye",
            "3": "Cream Bread",
            "4": "Akira hates bread",
            "answer": "Cream Bread"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who do Haruka and Sora go to live with at the end Sora's Route?",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "1": "Their grandparents",
            "2": "A friend of their parents",
            "3": "They lived  by themselves",
            "4": "Motoka",
            "answer": "A friend of their parents"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the route order in the anime?",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "1": "Common, Akira, Kazuha, Motoka, Nao and Sora",
            "2": "Common, Akira, Kazuha, Nao and Sora",
            "3": "Common, Kazuha, Akira, Motoka, Nao and Sora",
            "4": "Common, Kazuha, Akira, Nao and Sora",
            "answer": "Common, Kazuha, Akira, Nao and Sora"
        },
        {
            "question": "In the anime, which girl has the most sex scenes?",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "1": "Sora",
            "2": "Akira",
            "3": "Nao",
            "4": "Motoka",
            "answer": "Motoka"
        },
        {
            "question": "How many possible choices exist in the Yosuga no Sora visual novel?",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "1": "Three",
            "2": "Four",
            "3": "Five",
            "4": "One",
            "answer": "Four"
        },
        {
            "question": "What does 'Shishou' mean in English?",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "1": "Whiskers",
            "2": "Master",
            "3": "Love",
            "4": "Fluffy",
            "answer": "Master"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who is the first person (Besides Sora) to talk to Haruka in the visual novel?",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "1": "Kazuha",
            "2": "Nao",
            "3": "Kozue",
            "4": "Akira",
            "answer": "Nao"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which girl is a member of the swim club?",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "1": "Akira",
            "3": "Nao",
            "4": "Kozue",
            "answer": "Nao"
        },
        {   
            "question": "What does Haruka offer Sora as a snack on their train ride to the country?",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "1": "Chocolate",
            "2": "Pocky",
            "3": "It isn't stated",
            "4": "Dick",
            "answer": "Pocky"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who was considered the smartest during the study session at Akira's?",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "1": "Sora",
            "2": "Class Rep",
            "3": "Nao",
            "4": "Kazuha",
            "answer": "Sora"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is Kazuha suggestion to Akira on 'How to become Smart'?",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "1": "Eat right",
            "2": "Study",
            "3": "Stop sleeping in class",
            "4": "Stop drawing in her notes",
            "answer": "Stop drawing in her notes"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which character has a yukata sprite?",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "1": "Akira",
            "2": "Sora",
            "3": "Kazuha",
            "4": "Ryouhei",
            "answer": "Kazuha"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who takes Sora's measurements in Sora's route?",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "1": "Akira",
            "2": "Nao",
            "3": "Haruka",
            "4": "Herself",
            "answer": "Haruka"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who helps Sora put on her uniform in Akira's route?",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "1": "Haru",
            "2": "Nao",
            "3": "Class Rep",
            "4": "Akira",
            "answer": "Akira"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who was the voice actress for Sora in the anime?",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "1": "Hiroko Taguchi",
            "2": "Yuka Inokuchi",
            "3": "Sai Ushirono ",
            "4": "Haruka Shiranami",
            "answer": "Hiroko Taguchi"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who was the voice actress for Sora in the Visual Novel?",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "1": "Hiroko Taguchi",
            "2": "Yuka Inokuchi",
            "3": "Sai Ushirono ",
            "4": "Haruka Shiranami",
            "answer": "Hiroko Taguchi"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who was the voice actress for Akira in the visual novel?",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "1": "Mana Tsukishiro",
            "2": "Kayo Sakata",
            "3": "Hiroko Taguchi",
            "4": "Yuko Natsuyoshi",
            "answer": "Mana Tsukishiro"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who was the voice actress for Akira in the anime?",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "1": "Mana Tsukishiro",
            "2": "Kayo Sakata",
            "3": "Hiroko Taguchi",
            "4": "Yuko Natsuyoshi",
            "answer": "Kayo Sakata"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who was the voice actress for Nao in the anime?",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "1": "Kayo Sakata",
            "2": "Yuka Inokuchi",
            "3": "Mana Tsukishiro ",
            "4": "Ryoko Ono",
            "answer": "Yuka Inokuchi"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who was the voice actress for Nao in the VN?",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "1": "Kayo Sakata",
            "2": "Yuka Inokuchi",
            "3": "Mana Tsukishiro ",
            "4": "Ryoko Ono",
            "answer": "Yuka Inokuchi"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who was the voice actress for Kazuha in the VN?",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "1": "Yuka Inokuchi",
            "2": "Mana Tsukishiro",
            "3": "Ryoko Ono",
            "4": "Tomori Kusunoki",
            "answer": "Ryoko Ono"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who was the voice actress for Kazuha in the anime?",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "1": "Yuka Inokuchi",
            "2": "Hiroko Taguchi",
            "3": "Tomori Kusunoki",
            "4": "Ryoko Ono",
            "answer": "Ryoko Ono"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who was the voice actress for Kozue in the anime?",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "1": "Yukari Minegishi ",
            "2": "Ryoko Ono",
            "3": "Tae Okajima",
            "4": "Uncredited voice actress",
            "answer": "Yukari Minegishi"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who was the voice actress for Kozue in the VN?",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "1": "Yukari Minegishi ",
            "2": "Ryoko Ono",
            "3": "Tae Okajima",
            "4": "Uncredited voice actress",
            "answer": "Yukari Minegishi"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who was the voice actress for Motoka in the anime?",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "1": "Tae Okajima",
            "2": "Ryoko Tanaka",
            "3": "Sai Ushirono",
            "4": "Hiroko Taguchi",
            "answer": "Tae Okajima"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who was the voice actress for Motoka in the VN?",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "1": "Tae Okajima",
            "2": "Ryoko Tanaka",
            "3": "Sai Ushirono",
            "4": "Motoka does not appear in the anime",
            "answer": ""
        },
        {
            "question": "Who was the voice actress for Yahiro in the anime?",
            "difficulty": "hard,",
            "1": "Tae Okajima",
            "2": "Ryoko Tanaka",
            "3": "Sai Ushirono",
            "4": "Hiroko Taguchi",
            "answer": "Ryoko Tanaka"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who was the voice acress for Yahiro in the VN?",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "1": "Ai Kayano",
            "2": "Shizuru Nakatsu",
            "3": "Ryoko Tanaka",
            "4": "Yahiro does not appear in the VN",
            "answer": "Ryoko Tanaka"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who was the voice actor for Ryouhei in the VN?",
            "Difficulty": "hard",
            "1": "Yoshitsugu Matsuoka",
            "2": "Sai Ushirono ",
            "3": "Hiro Shimono",
            "4": "Takurou Nakakuni",
            "answer": "Sai Ushirono"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who was the voice actor for Ryouhei in the anime?",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "1": "Yoshitsugu Matsuoka",
            "2": "Sai Ushirono ",
            "3": "Hiro Shimono",
            "4": "Takurou Nakakuni",
            "answer": "Takurou Nakakuni"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who was the voice actor for Haru in the VN?",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "1": "Takurou Nakakuni ",
            "2": "Sai Ushirono",
            "3": "Hiroko Taguchi",
            "4": "Haru is not voiced in the VN",
            "answer": ""
        },
        {
            "question": "Who was the primary voice actor for Haru in the anime?",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "1": "Hiro Shimono",
            "2": "Sai Ushirono",
            "3": "Hiroko Taguchi",
            "4": "Megumi Matsumoto",
            "answer": "Hiro Shimono"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who voiced child Haru in the anime?",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "1": "Hiro Shimono",
            "2": "Sai Ushirono",
            "3": "Hiroko Taguchi",
            "4": "Megumi Matsumoto",
            "answer": "Megumi Matsumoto"
        },
        {
            "question": "When was the Yosuga no Sora Visual Novel first released?",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "1": "July 27th 2007",
            "2": "May 1st 2007",
            "3": "October 8th 2010",
            "4": "December 5th 2008",
            "answer": "December 5th 2008"
        },
        {
            "question": "When did the Yosuga no Sora Anime first premier",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "1": "October 8th 2010",
            "2": "October 4th 2010",
            "3": "December 5th 2008",
            "4": "June 15th 2012",
            "answer": "October 4th 2010"
        },
        {
            "question": "When was the original run for the Yosuga no Sora manga?",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "1": "December 5th 2008-April 11th 2009",
            "2": "February 2nd 2012-Ongoing",
            "3": "Febuary 3rd 2012-Ongoing",
            "4": "May 26th 2010-December 25th 2010",
            "answer": "May 26th 2010-December 25th 2010"
        },
        {
            "question": "How many routes are in the Visual Novel?",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "1": "3",
            "2": "4",
            "3": "5",
            "4": "6",
            "answer": "5"
        },
        {
            "question": "How many routes are in the anime?",
            "difficulty": "Medium",
            "1": "3",
            "2": "4",
            "3": "5",
            "4": "6",
            "answer": "5"
        },
        {
            "question": "How many routes are in Haruka na Sora?",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "1": "2",
            "2": "3",
            "3": "5",
            "4": "10",
            "answer": "3"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of these is not found in the Yosuga no Sora anime soundtrack?",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "1": "Kioku ",
            "2": "Old memory",
            "3": "Before it's too late",
            "4": "Dearly Beloved",
            "answer": ""
        },
        {
            "question": "Who is the best character in Yosuga no Sora?",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "1": "Yahiro",
            "2": "Yahiro",
            "3": "Yahiro",
            "4": "ME",
            "answer": "Akira"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which girl is Sora closest to?",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "1": "Akira",
            "2": "Nao",
            "3": "Kazuha",
            "4": "Class Rep",
            "answer": "Akira"
        },
        {
            "question": "What does Nao's surname mean?",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "1": "'Rely on, be dependent upon' (依) (yori) and 'princess' (姫) (hime).",
            "2": "'Water' (依) (yori) 'edge' (姫) (hime)",
            "3": "'Water's edge' (渚) (Migiwa)",
            "4": "'Sky' (穹) (Amatsume)",
            "answer": "'Rely on, be dependent upon' (依) (yori) and 'princess' (姫) (hime)."
        },
        {
            "question": "What type of phone does Sora have?",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "1": "Samsung 931SC",
            "2": "Nokia 3310",
            "3": "Original Iphone",
            "4": "She does not own a phone",
            "answer": "Samsung 931SC"
        },
        {
            "question": "How tall is Kazuha?",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "1": "160 cm",
            "2": "162 cm",
            "3": "170 cm",
            "4": "164 cm",
            "answer": "164 cm"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who owns Shishou?",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "1": "Sora",
            "2": "Akira",
            "3": "Kazuha",
            "4": "He is a stray cat",
            "answer": "Akira"
        }
    ]
}

